export const QuizData = [
    {
      question: "What is meant by MURI Record?",
      options: [
        "a. MURI records are only for sports.",
        "b. MURI records achievements in Indonesia.",
        "c. MURI is an award from Guinness.",
        "d. MURI is given to everyone."
      ],
      correctAnswer: "b. MURI records achievements in Indonesia.",
    },
    {
      question: "What Indonesian heritage is recognized by UNESCO, except?",
      options: [
        "a. Wayang",
        "b. Iron",
        "c. Batik",
        "d. Keris"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "b. Iron",
    },
    {
      question: "Where does the Saman dance originate from?",
      options: [
        "a. West Java",
        "b.  South Sulawesi",
        "c. Aceh",
        "d. Bali"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "c. Aceh",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the traditional musical instrument from West Java made of bamboo?",
      options: [
        "a. Angklung",
        "b. Tiva",
        "c. Kendang",
        "d. Sasando"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "a. Angklung",
    },
    {
      question: "Wayang kulit is a traditional performance art from which region?",
      options: [
        "a. South Sumatra",
        "b. Papua",
        "c. West Kalimantan",
        "d. Central Java"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "d. Central Java",
    },
    {
      question: "Where does Borobudur Temple come from?",
      options: [
        "a. Bali",
        "b. Central Java",
        "c. Kalimantan",
        "d. Papua"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "b. Central Java",
    },
    {
      question: "Where does the Kolintang musical instrument come from?",
      options: [
        "a. Bali",
        "b. West Java",
        "c. South Sumatra",
        "d. North Sulawesi"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "d. North Sulawesi",
    },
    {
      question: "How many provinces are there in indonesia?",
      options: [
        "a. 27",
        "b. 38",
        "c. 28",
        "d. 36"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "b. 38",
    },
    {
      question: "Where does the Joglo traditional house come from?",
      options: [
        "a. Minangkabau",
        "b. Sulawesi",
        "c. Kalimantan",
        "d. Yogyakarta"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "d. Yogyakarta",
    },
    {
      question: "Where does the traditional Gamelan musical instrument come from?",
      options: [
        "a. Java & Bali",
        "b. South Sumatra",
        "c. Kalimantan",
        "d. Maluku"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "a. Java & Bali",
    },
    
];